<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="1">
        <record id="workshop_project_stage_running" model="project.task.type">
            <field name="sequence">1</field>
            <field name="name">Running</field>
        </record>
        <record id="workshop_project_stage_done" model="project.task.type">
            <field name="sequence">2</field>
            <field name="name">Done</field>
        </record>
        <record id="project_project_workshop" model="project.project">
            <field name="name">Workshop</field>
            <field name="color">3</field>
            <field name="user_id" ref="base.user_admin"/>
            <field name="type_ids"
                   eval="[(4, ref('workshop.workshop_project_stage_running')),(4, ref('workshop.workshop_project_stage_done'))]"/>
            <field name="privacy_visibility">portal</field>
        </record>


        <record id="scope_of_work_data_1" model="workshop.scopeofwork">
            <field name="name">Scope Of Work</field>
            <field name="description">A machine is a physical system using power to apply forces and control movement to perform an action. The term is commonly applied to artificial devices, such as those employing engines or motors, but also to natural biological macromolecules, such as molecular machines. Machines can be driven by animals and people.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="extend_of_quotes_data_1" model="workshop.extend.quotes">
            <field name="name">Extend Of Quotes</field>
            <field name="description">If any work found necessary during the course of rewinding/overhauling other than the specified in the “scope of work” will be carried out with your prior approval, at an extra cost and time.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="payment_terms_data_1" model="workshop.payment.terms">
            <field name="name">Payment Term</field>
            <field name="description">Within 30 Days from the date of delivery</field>
        </record>

        <record id="testing_inspection_data_1" model="workshop.testing.inspection">
            <field name="name">Testing And Inspection</field>
            <field name="description">Carry out voltage drop, Impedance, and winding resistance test. Carry out Mechanical check on Bearing Journals and Bearing Housing, run test the motor in our works and record the results</field>
        </record>

        <record id="warranty_data_1" model="workshop.warranty">
            <field name="name">Warranty</field>
            <field name="description">Our work will be guaranteed against the use of defective materials and/or workmanship for a period of 3 months from the date of dispatch ONLY FOR
THE WORK CARRIED OUT under the standard maintaining conditions.
The client has a responsibility to operate service and maintain the equipment at all times in accordance with the recommendations of the Original
Equipment Manufacturer
Proper engineering practice for such equipment Days.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="delivery_data_1" model="workshop.delivery">
            <field name="name">Delivery</field>
            <field name="description">7 Working days from the date of confirmation.</field>
        </record>

    </data>
</odoo>